leaderbank.com 2004-12-05

# Leader Bank

| 

> **_Please click here to read our Privacy Policy frequently asked questions_**
> 
> **_Please click here to read about identity theft_**
> 
> **LEADER BANK  
>  **  
>  **PRIVACY POLICY DISCLOSURE  
>  **(Protection of the Privacy of Non-Public Information)  
>    
>  Respecting and protecting customer privacy is vital to our business. By explaining our Privacy Policy to you, we trust that you will better understand how we keep our customer information private and secure while using it to serve you better. Keeping customer information secure is a top priority, and we are disclosing our policies to help you understand how we handle the personal information about you that we collect and disclose. The provisions of this notice will apply to former customers as well as current customers unless stated otherwise. **The Privacy Policy Explains the Following:  
>  **
> 
>   * Protecting the confidentiality of our customer information. 
> 
> 

>   * Who is covered by the Privacy Policy. 
> 
> 

>   * How we gather information. 
> 
> 

>   * The types of information we share, why and with whom.  
> 
> 
> 

> 
> **Protecting the Confidentiality of Customer Information:  
>  **
> 
> We take our responsibility to protect the privacy and confidentiality of customer information very seriously. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to store and secure information about you from unauthorized access, alteration, and destruction. Our control policies, for example, authorize access to customer information only by individuals who need access to do their work.
> 
> From time to time, we enter into agreements with other companies to provide services to us or make products and services available to you. Under these agreements, the companies may receive information about you but they must safeguard this information, and they may not use it for any other purpose.
> 
> **Who is Covered by the Privacy Policy:  
>  **
> 
> We provide our Privacy Policy to customers when they conduct business with our company. If we change our privacy policies to permit us to share additional information we have about you as described below, or to permit disclosures to additional types of parties, you will be notified in advance. This Privacy Policy applies to consumers who are current customers or former customers.  
> 
> 
> **How We Gather Information:  
>  **
> 
> As part of providing you with financial products or services, we may obtain information about you from the following sources:  
> 
> 
>   * Applications, forms, and other information that you provide to us whether in writing, in person, by telephone, electronically, or by any other means. This information may include your name, address, employment information, income, and credit references.  
> 
> 
> 

>   * Your transaction with us, our affiliates, or others. This information may include your account balances, payment history, and account usage.  
> 
> 
> 

>   * Consumer reporting agencies. This information may include account information and information about your credit worthiness.  
> 
> 
> 

>   * Public sources. This information may include real estate records, employment records, telephone numbers, etc.  
> 
> 
> 

> 
> **Information We Share:  
>  **
> 
> We may disclose information we have about you as permitted by law. We are required to or we may provide information about you to third parties without your consent, as permitted by law, such as:  
> 
> 
>   * To regulatory authorities and law enforcement officials.  
> 
> 
> 

>   * To protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud, unauthorized transactions, claims, or other liability.   
> 
> 
> 

>   * To report account activity to credit bureaus.  
> 
> 
> 

>   * To consumer reporting agencies.  
> 
> 
> 

>   * To respond to a subpoena or court order, judicial process or regulatory authorities.  
> 
> 
> 

>   * In connection with a proposed or actual sale, merger, or transfer of all or a portion of a business or an operating unit, etc.  
> 
> 
> 

> 
>   
>  In addition, we may provide information about you to our service providers to help us process your applications or service your accounts. Our service providers may include billing service providers, mail and telephone service companies, lenders, investors, title and escrow companies, appraisal companies, etc.
> 
> We may also provide information about you to our service providers to help us perform marketing services. This information provided to these service providers may include the categories of information described above under “How We Gather Information” limited to only that which we deem appropriate for these service providers to carry out their functions.
> 
> We do not provide information about you to any company whose products and services are being marketed unless you authorize us to do so. These companies are not allowed to use this information for purposes beyond your specific authorization.
> 
> **Our Security Procedures:  
>  **
> 
> Access to your personal and account information is restricted to those employees who need to know that information as part of their job, to service your account or to provide products and services to you. We maintain physical electronic and procedural safeguards that are reasonably designed to guard your nonpublic personal information.  
> 
> 
> **Accuracy of Customer Information:  
>  **
> 
> We recognize that the accuracy of your personal and account information is critical to you and to that end we follow procedures to reasonably ensure the accuracy of your information. If you find that any information we have on file or have reported to another party does not appear to be accurate, please write to us at:  
> 
> 
> **LEADER BANK  
>  **141 Massachusetts Avenue  
>  Arlington, MA 02474 Please include your account number.  
> 
> 
> This privacy policy statement applies to individuals and not business entities. We reserve the right to make changes to this statement. The statement is for general guidance and does not constitute a contract, not does it modify or amend agreements we have with you.
